Guide to the Frank Moore Papers MSS.135
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Art Files
  - Subseries D: Other Artists
    - Driver, Sara, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 457)
    - Dugdale, John, 1994-1999 (Box 10, Folder 458)
    - E., Ethyl, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 459)
    - Elmslie, Kenward, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 460)
    - Episalla, Joy, 1996-2001 (Box 10, Folder 461)
    - de Fazio, John [additional materials in oversize box], 19992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 462)
    - Feher, Tony, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 463)
    - Frame, Allen [additional materials in oversize box], 1990-1996 (Box 10, Folder 464)
    - Friedman, Dan, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 465)
    - Fulton, Hamish, undated (Box 10, Folder 466)
    - Futura 2000, undated (Box 10, Folder 467)
    - Garbe, William, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 468)
    - Gober, Robert, 1985-1994 (Box 10, Folder 469)
    - Goldin, Nan, ca. 1994 (Box 10, Folder 470)
    - Graham, Dan, undated (Box 10, Folder 471)
    - Green, Elliot, undated (Box 10, Folder 472)
    - Green, Gregory, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 473)
    - Guilliatt, Lee, undated (Box 10, Folder 474)
    - Gundersen, Bruce, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 475)
    - Gunderson, Greta, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 476)
    - Hammond, Jane, 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 477)
    - Handorff, Joel, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 478)
    - Hannah, Duncan, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 479)
    - Haring, Keith, 1981-1999 (Box 10, Folder 480)
    - Harte, Glynn Boyd [additional materials located in oversize box], 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 481)
    - Hashey, Jan, 1984-19988 (Box 10, Folder 482)
    - Hawkins, Robert, ca. 1987 (Box 10, Folder 483)
    - Hawkins, William L., 1997 (Box 10, Folder 484)
    - Hayden, Victor, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 485)
    - Henderson, Edward, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 486)
    - Henry, Janet, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 487)
    - Hodermarsky, Maria, undated (Box 10, Folder 488)
    - Horn, Richard, undated (Box 10, Folder 489)
    - Hujar, Peter, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 490)
    - Hull, Greg, undated (Box 10, Folder 491)
    - Humphrey, David, 1993-1998 (Box 10, Folder 492)
    - Hunter, Francine, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 493)
    - Michael, Hurson, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 494)
    - Juarez, Roberto, 1981-1994 (Box 10, Folder 495)
    - Kardon, Dennis, ca. 1996 (Box 10, Folder 496)
    - Kelly, John a.k.a. Dogmar Onassis, 1987-1991 (Box 10, Folder 497)
    - Kennard, John, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 498)
    - Kortick, Roy, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 499)
    - Kramer, Larry, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 500)
    - LeDray, Charles, undated (Box 10, Folder 501)
    - Leibowitz, Cary, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 502)
    - Longendyke, Paula, undated (Box 10, Folder 503)
    - Lukacs, Attila Richard, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 504)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 10, Folder 505)
    - McClatchy, J.D., undated (Box 10, Folder 506)
    - Marten, Ruth, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 507)
    - Martin, Chris, 1988-1995 (Box 10, Folder 508)
    - Melle, undated (Box 10, Folder 509)
    - Metz, Mike, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 510)
    - Miller, Steve, 1982-1993 (Box 10, Folder 511)
    - Milow, Keith, ca. 1993 (Box 10, Folder 512)
    - Minagawa, Yasuo, undated (Box 10, Folder 513)
    - Miro, Joan, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 514)
    - Morper, Daniel, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 515)
    - Mueller, Cookie [additional materials in oversize box], undated (Box 10, Folder 516)
    - Mueller, Stephen, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 517)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 10, Folder 518)
    - Nauman, Bruce, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 519)
    - Nechvatal, Joseph, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 520)
    - Negroponte, George, 1985-1998 (Box 10, Folder 521)
    - Nelson, Joan, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 522)
    - Neshat, Shirin, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 523)
    - O'Connor, Tere, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 524)
    - Oji, Helen, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 525)
    - Ontani, Luigi, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 526)
    - Osorio, Pepon, 1991-1996 (Box 10, Folder 527)
    - Otterness, Tom, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 528)
    - Pines, Lisa, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 529)
    - Potterat, Anne-Francoise, undated (Box 10, Folder 530)
    - Pousette-Dart, Joanna, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 531)
    - Pozzi, Lucio, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 532)
    - Rand, Archie, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 533)
    - Rhein, Eric, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 534)
    - Riopelle, Jean-Paul, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 535)
    - Rockman, Alexis, undated (Box 10, Folder 536)
    - Rosen, Jane, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 537)
    - Rosenquist, James, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 538)
    - Salerno, Linda, undated (Box 10, Folder 539)
    - Santore, Joseph, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 540)
    - Sarfati, Patrick [additional items located in oversize box], 1978-1984 (Box 10, Folder 541)
    - Sovinio, Alberto, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 542)
    - Scharf, Kenny, ca. 1995 (Box 10, Folder 543)
    - Schlesinger, Peter, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 544)
    - Self, Jim [additional materials in oversize box], 1981-2000 (Box 10, Folder 545)
    - Self, Jim. Cunningham Studio June-July 1980 (Box 10, Folder 546)
    - Self, Jim. Dance Theater Workshop. Fall 1980 (Box 10, Folder 547)
    - Self, Jim. Jacob's Pillow, undated (Box 10, Folder 548)
    - Self, Jim at MoMA, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 549)
    - Seymour, Dermot, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 550)
    - Shaver, Nancy, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 551)
    - Shils, E.B., undated (Box 10, Folder 552)
    - Simons, Tom, undated (Box 10, Folder 553)
    - Slaughter, Tom, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 554)
    - Smith, Gregory, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 555)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 10, Folder 556)
    - Smith, Philip, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 557)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 10, Folder 558)
    - Stalin, John, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 559)
    - Steers, Hugh, 1993-1998 (Box 10, Folder 560)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 10, Folder 561)
    - Stoll, George, 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 562)
    - Taylor, Steed, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 563)
    - Tisa, Ken, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 564)
    - Tuttle, Richard, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 566)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 10, Folder 567)
    - Warhol, Andy, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 568)
    - Warren, Rosanna [additional materials in oversize box], 1984-1995 (Box 10, Folder 569)
    - Winokur, Neil [additional materials in oversize box], 1982-1989 (Box 10, Folder 570)
    - Winters, Robin, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 571)
    - Wojnarowicz, David [additional materials in oversize box], ca. 1989 (Box 11, Folder 572)
    - Woodruf, Thomas, 1991-1999 (Box 11, Folder 573)
    - Wootton, Cynthia, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 574)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 11, Folder 575)
    - Group shows, performances, projects and events, undated (Box 11, Folder 576)
    - Miscellaneous [additional materials in oversize box], undated (Box 11, Folder 577)
- Series III: Correspondence and Manuscripts
  This series includes correspondence, primarily documents written to Moore and manuscripts. The series is organized into four subseries; A: Last Names, subseries B: First Name Only, subseries C: Miscellaneous, Illegible or Unindicated and subseries D: Manuscripts. Materials in this series are organized alphabetically.
  - Subseries A: Last Name
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 11, Folder 578)
    - Alago, Michael, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 579)
    - Andrews, Frank, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 580)
    - Atkins, Shawn of House of Frame by Frame Fierce., 2001 (Box 11, Folder 581)
    - Berg, Henry, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 582)
    - Bergtold, Amy, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 583)
    - Bergtold, Paul, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 584)
    - Bibo, James Stuart, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 585)
    - Bishop, James, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 586)
    - Blane, Marc, 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 587)
    - Brainard, Joe, 1988-1993 (Box 11, Folder 588)
    - Buddhayana, ca. 1996 (Box 11, Folder 589)
    - Bush, Bob, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 590)
    - Cadmus, Paul, 1982-1998 (Box 11, Folder 591)
    - Carriere, Jennifer and Mathieu, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 592)
    - Cemo, Guiseppe, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 593)
    - Chaet, Bernard, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 594)
    - Christo and Jeanne Claude, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 595)
    - Chu, Ken, undated (Box 11, Folder 596)
    - City of New York Department of Cultural Affairs., undated (Box 11, Folder 597)
    - Clarke, Robert, 1994-1997 (Box 11, Folder 598)
    - Claudia Gian Ferrari Gallery of Contemporary Art, Milan, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 599)
    - Contemporary Arts Center [additional materials in oversize box], 1994 (Box 11, Folder 600)
    - CVI, undated (Box 11, Folder 601)
    - D'Agostino, Roberto, undated (Box 11, Folder 602)
    - Dance Theater Workshop, undated (Box 11, Folder 603)
    - Desert, Ultrick, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 604)
    - Elsmlie, Kenward, 1989-1994 (Box 11, Folder 605)
    - Elovich, Richard, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 606)
    - Family Correspondence to Frank, 1977-1999 (Box 11, Folder 607)
    - Fearey, Don, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 608)
    - Frame, Allen, undated (Box 11, Folder 609)
    - Golson, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 610)
    - Gutierrez-Solana, Carlos, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 611)
    - Hall, Steven, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 612)
    - Hammond, Jane, ca. 1994 (Box 11, Folder 613)
    - Harris, Don, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 614)
    - Harris, Sarah Burt, undated (Box 11, Folder 615)
    - Harris, William, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 616)
    - Harte, Glynn Boyd, undated (Box 11, Folder 617)
    - Hatchondo, Anne-Marie and Michel Reilhac, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 618)
    - Hawkins, Ashton, undated (Box 11, Folder 619)
    - Hendricks, Geoffrey, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 620)
    - HIV Related Violence Project. Found in book 672, Epidemic of Fear., undated (Box 11, Folder 621)
    - Holzman, Eric, undated (Box 11, Folder 622)
    - Humphrey, David, undated (Box 11, Folder 623)
    - Independent Curators Incorporated, undated (Box 11, Folder 624)
    - Interview Magazine, undated (Box 11, Folder 625)
    - Iseman, Ellen, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 626)
    - Jernigan, Candy, 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 627)
    - Juarez, Roberto, undated (Box 11, Folder 628)
    - Kerr, Alex, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 629)
    - Kiehl, David, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 630)
    - Knowlton, Win, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 631)
    - Korb, Carolyn, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 632)
    - Kramer, Richard, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 632A)
    - Krueck, Anstisr, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 633)
    - LaNasa, Katherine, undated (Box 11, Folder 634)
    - LeCasble, Olivia, 1985-1998 (Box 11, Folder 635)
    - Leiber, David, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 636)
    - Leibowitz, Cary. a.k.a. Candyass [additional materials in oversize box], 1994-1995 (Box 11, Folder 637)
    - Lesbian and Gay Rights Project, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 638)
    - Lopez, Martina, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 639)
    - Maurer, Janet, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 640)
    - McCrudden, Ira, undated (Box 11, Folder 641)
    - McCuinness, Hugh, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 642)
    - Medgar Evers College, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 643)
    - Melaney, Adam, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 644)
    - Moore, Frank. Letters from Frank Moore to assorted others., undated (Box 11, Folder 645)
    - Moore, Frank. Letters from Frank Moore to his parents., undated (Box 11, Folder 646)
    - Moore, Patrick. Director of the Estate Project for Artists with AIDS., 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 647)
    - Moore, Rebecca, 1990-1998 (Box 11, Folder 648)
    - Moore, Rosalind, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 649)
    - Murray, Elizabeth, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 650)
    - Owens, Philip, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 651)
    - Pasmasambhava Buddhist Center, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 652)
    - Pamela Auchincloss Gallery, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 653)
    - Patterson, David, undated (Box 11, Folder 654)
    - Patterson, Pat and Bob, undated (Box 11, Folder 655)
    - Paz, Alicia, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 656)
    - Peterson, Shawn, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 657)
    - Petty, Lisa, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 658)
    - Pirmar [?], John, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 659)
    - Pozzi, Lucio, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 660)
    - Provine, Dorothy, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 661)
    - Pujol-Courmarian, Alain, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 662)
    - Reich, Frank, ca. 1977 (Box 11, Folder 663)
    - Rockman, Alexis, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 664)
    - Rowell, Patricia, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 665)
    - Sandrow, Hope, ca. 1994 (Box 11, Folder 666)
    - Sarfati, Patrick, 1980-1997 (Box 11, Folder 667)
    - Scott, Sue, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 668)
    - Self, Jim, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 669)
    - Sheridon, Laurie, ca. 1996 (Box 11, Folder 670)
    - Sillman, Amy, ca. 1994 (Box 11, Folder 671)
    - Simon, Sue, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 672)
    - Skidmore College, Tang Teaching Museum and Art Gallery., 2001 (Box 11, Folder 673)
    - Smith, Eileen, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 674)
    - Sperone Westwater, undated (Box 11, Folder 675)
    - Stanton, Todd, undated (Box 11, Folder 676)
    - Stefantos, Maria Elena, undated (Box 11, Folder 677)
    - Strompf, Steve, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 678)
    - Taylor, Steed, ca. 1995 (Box 11, Folder 679)
    - Teruko, Kiyoshi, undated (Box 11, Folder 680)
    - Tisa, Ken, undated (Box 11, Folder 681)
    - Traglio, Carlo, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 682)
    - Visual AIDS, 1997-2001 (Box 11, Folder 683)
    - Warner, Michael, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 684)
    - Warren, Rosanna, 1975-2000 (Box 11, Folder 685)
    - Webster, Stephen, 1981-1986 (Box 11, Folder 686)
    - Wemega-Kwawo, Rikki, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 687)
    - Werthmann, Colleen, undated (Box 11, Folder 688)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1996-2002 (Box 11, Folder 689)
    - Wilson, Robert, 1985-1999 (Box 11, Folder 690)
    - Winslow, Kirk, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 691)
    - Wood, Suzy Mallory, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 692)
    - Woodruff, Tom, undated (Box 11, Folder 693)
    - Young, Virgil, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 694)
  - Subseries B: First Name Only
    - Barry, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 695)
    - Betsy, 1992-1998 (Box 11, Folder 696)
    - Bobby R., 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 697)
    - Brad, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 698)
    - Bro-bro, undated (Box 11, Folder 699)
    - Buzz, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 700)
    - Carlos, 1989-1996 (Box 11, Folder 701)
    - Cecile and Steve, 1989-1996 (Box 11, Folder 702)
    - Coco, 1982-1986 (Box 11, Folder 703)
    - D., ca. 1983 (Box 11, Folder 704)
    - Dennis, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 705)
    - Elain, undated (Box 11, Folder 706)
    - Fred, ca. 2001 (Box 11, Folder 707)
    - Gaby, undated (Box 11, Folder 708)
    - George, 1978-1988 (Box 11, Folder 709)
    - Gladys, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 710)
    - Hamey, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 711)
    - Heys, undated (Box 11, Folder 712)
    - Jan, 1980-1997 (Box 11, Folder 713)
    - Jim, 1983-1991 (Box 11, Folder 714)
    - John, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 715)
    - Kynaston, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 716)
    - L., 1977-1987 (Box 11, Folder 717)
    - Laurie, 1975-1981 (Box 11, Folder 718)
    - Liz, ca. 1993 (Box 11, Folder 719)
    - Mara Jayne, ca. 1996 (Box 11, Folder 720)
    - Marc, 1991-1994 (Box 11, Folder 721)
    - Mario, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 722)
    - Martha, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 723)
    - Michael and Robert, 1983-1994 (Box 11, Folder 724)
    - Nancy, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 725)
    - Phil and Martha, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 726)
    - Pierre, 1978-1983 (Box 11, Folder 727)
    - Policewoman, ca. 1992 (Box 11, Folder 728)
    - Shawn, undated (Box 11, Folder 729)
    - Sophie, 1985-1990 (Box 11, Folder 730)
    - Tom, undated (Box 11, Folder 731)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous, Illegible and Unsigned
    - Miscellaneous, illegible or unsigned correspondence, undated (Box 12, Folder 732)
    - Miscellaneous, illegible or unsigned correspondence, undated (Box 12, Folder 733)
    - Miscellaneous, illegible or unsigned correspondence, undated (Box 12, Folder 734)
  - Subseries D: Manuscripts
    - "Vajrachedicka Prajnaparamita [sic] The Diamond cutter wisdom that has gone beyond, or, the Diamond Sutra." handwritten., undated (Box 12, Folder 735)
- Series IV: Source Material
  This series contains seven subseries; Subseries A: magazines, Subseries B: catalogues, Subseries C: images, Subseries D: articles, Subseries E: photographs, Subseries F: books and Subseries G: ephemera. These materials served as research, inspiration and models for Frank Moore's artwork. Where possible, materials are organized alphabetically by author or title.
  - Subseries A: Magazines
    - American Horticulturalist, June 1995 (Box 12, Folder 736)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 12, Folder 737)
    - Item removed to oversize, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 738)
    - Hunter Trader Trapper. volume 46 number 4, July 1923 (Box 12, Folder 739)
    - International Wildlife. volume 13 number 6, November-December 1983 (Box 12, Folder 740)
    - National Geographic. volume 184 number 4, October 1993. (Box 12, Folder 741)
    - National Geographic. Volume 185 number 2, February 1994 (Box 12, Folder 742)
    - Nest: A Quarterly of Interiors. Spring 2001 (Box 12, Folder 743)
    - New York Times Magazine. January 30, 2000. (Box 12, Folder 744)
    - U.S. News and World Report. March 25, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 745)
    - WIRED. February 2001. (Box 12, Folder 746)
  - Subseries B: Catalogues and Manuals
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 12, Folder 747)
    - Dover Antiques and Photography, undated (Box 12, Folder 748)
    - Dujardin Machines, undated (Box 12, Folder 749)
    - Gordon Novelty Co. Inc. Catalogue, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 750)
    - The Gulf Specimen Co., undated (Box 12, Folder 751)
    - Jones and Scully Inc. Orchidglade, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 752)
    - Lakeland Nursery Catalogue, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 753)
    - Manny's Millinery Supply Co. Spring 1991. (Box 12, Folder 754)
    - Regina Twinbrush Floor Polisher and Scrubber: Instructions and Care, undated (Box 12, Folder 755)
    - Robots, Industry booklets, undated (Box 12, Folder 756)
    - Rubber Stamp Catalogues, undated (Box 12, Folder 757)
    - Somes Uniforms: Confidential Price List, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 758)
    - Some's Uniforms Inc., undated (Box 12, Folder 759)
    - Unisted States Postal Service Fifty State Birds and Flowers Mint Set catalogue., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 760)
    - William Henry Maule Philadelphia, Seeds., 1885 (Box 12, Folder 761)
  - Subseries C: Clippings, Articles, Subject files
    - AIDS articles and research, undated (Box 12, Folder 762)
    - Araeen, Rasheed. Opinion Piece "Save the Johannesburg Biennale/Sao Paulo and the Africans", 2001 (Box 12, Folder 763)
    - Biotech Articles, 1999-2001 (Box 12, Folder 764)
    - Butterfly Gardening: Insect beauties flock to colorful, nectar-rich flowers, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 765)
    - Calligraphy and Fonts, undated (Box 12, Folder 766)
    - Cowboys. Cattlemen's Days Gunnison Colorado, Travel information Laramie, Wyoming. [additional materials in oversize box], 1998 (Box 12, Folder 767)
    - Diving Information, undated (Box 12, Folder 768)
    - Durning, Alan Thein. "Saving the Forests: What will it take?" World Watch Paper number 117, December 1993 (Box 12, Folder 769)
    - The Gene Media Forum, Transcript. September 20, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 770)
    - Genetic Engineering Articles, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 771)
    - Genetics and genome project articles, 1992-2002 (Box 12, Folder 772)
    - Great Lakes Water Quality Board, 1993 Report to the International Joint Commission. (Box 12, Folder 773)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings, undated (Box 12, Folder 774)
    - Miscellaneous Pamphlets, undated (Box 12, Folder 775)
    - Niagara research, undated (Box 12, Folder 776)
    - Protein Power Pamphlet from 21st Century Genetics, undated (Box 12, Folder 777)
    - Roller Coasters, 1983-1994 (Box 12, Folder 778)
    - Scrapbook containing clippings on European Art, History, Geography and Architecture, undated (Box 12, Folder 779)
    - Sicily, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 780)
    - Story Board example, undated (Box 13, Folder 781)
    - Treaty Oak photographs and news stories [additional materials in oversize box], 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 782)
    - Wigstock, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 783)
    - Yosemite, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 784)
  - Subseries D: Images
    - "Anatomy Theatre, 1610" with notes., undated (Box 13, Folder 785)
    - Audobon postcard folio, undated (Box 13, Folder 786)
    - AZT chemical diagram, undated (Box 13, Folder 787)
    - "Beacon" images, undated (Box 13, Folder 788)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 13, Folder 789)
    - Cards, undated (Box 13, Folder 790)
    - "Dance of Death at Basle", undated (Box 13, Folder 791)
    - Item removed to oversize, undated (Box 13, Folder 792)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 13, Folder 793)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 13, Folder 794)
    - "Expulsion from Paradise", undated (Box 13, Folder 795)
    - Farms, undated (Box 13, Folder 796)
    - "Freedom From Want" by Norman Rockwell. Gridded, used for "Freedom to Share", undated (Box 13, Folder 797)
    - Film stills, undated (Box 13, Folder 798)
    - Glamour Collections folder, undated (Box 13, Folder 799)
    - "Gulliver Awake" images, undated (Box 13, Folder 800)
    - Harlem Renaissance Day of Commitment fan. Wednesday, June 7, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 801)
    - Men. Postcards and Images in Jean Paul Gaultier Homme folder., undated (Box 13, Folder 802)
    - Miscellaneous images [additional materials in oversize box], undated (Box 13, Folder 803)
    - Scull Prints, undated (Box 13, Folder 804)
    - Niagara Falls [additional materials in oversize box], undated (Box 13, Folder 805)
    - Paint by Numbers (Box 13, Folder 806)
    - Large Postcards, undated (Box 13, Folder 807)
    - Shaker Design, undated (Box 13, Folder 808)
    - Tapestries featuring animals, undated (Box 13, Folder 809)
    - National Geographic Pamphlet, undated (Box 13, Folder 810)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 13, Folder 811)
    - Waterfalls, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 812)
    - woman, undated (Box 13, Folder 813)
    - Postcards, undated (Box 14)
  - Subseries E: Photographs
    - General photographs. Includes images of cows, national parks and miscellaneous photography., undated (Box 15, Folder data_value_missing_a682e1941548796a26d4a05a61dc6adf)
    - Niagara Falls [additional panoramic photographs in oversize box], undated (Box 16, Folder data_value_missing_65e05454550a5e68d8201194aca2653c)
    - Niagara Falls, continued, undated (Box 17, Folder data_value_missing_f62981a62531cfdb5f16f242bbb24471)
  - Subseries F: Ephemera
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 13, Folder 814)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 13, Folder 815)
    - Fringe, undated (Box 13, Folder 816)
    - Napkins, undated (Box 13, Folder 817)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 13, Folder 818)
    - Skeletons, posable, undated (Box 13, Folder 819)
    - Souvenirs, undated (Box 13, Folder 820)
  - Subseries G: Books
    - Allen, Glover Morrill. Birds and their Attributes., 1962 (Box 13, Folder 821)
    - Item removed to oversize (Box 13, Folder 822)
    - il Balletto repertorio del teatro di danza dal 1581, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 823)
    - Bardintzeff, Jacques-Marie and Alexander R. McBirney Volcanology 2nd edition., 2000 (Box 13, Folder 824)
    - Bentley, W.A. and W.J. Humphreys Snow Crystals. annotated, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 825)
    - Bourdon, David. Designing the Earth: The Human Impulse to Shape Nature., 1995 (Box 13, Folder 826)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Garden Record Handbook on Dwarfed Potted Trees: The Bonsai of Japan, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 827)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Garden Record Handbook on Orchids, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 828)
    - Budker, Paul The Life of Sharks, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 829)
    - Burton, Maurice. Introducing Life Under the Sea, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 830)
    - Burton, Maurice Under the Sea, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 831)
    - The Chinese Porcelain Company The Volcanoes of Italy, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 832)
    - Crimp, Douglas. AIDS Cultural Analysis, Cultural Activism. annotated, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 833)
    - Cruse, Julius M. and Robert E. Lewis Atlas of Immunology, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 834)
    - Cumming, Jane Scriven and Barbara Donahue. Gilmanton Summers: Memories of A New Hampshire Village in the Early 1900s., 1993 (Box 18, Folder 835)
    - Dorin, Henry Modern Principles of Chemistry, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 836)